

CONNECT ME

- Kannachan(H),Othukkungal(PO) Malappuram,Kerala
- arifkk0313@gmail.com

MOB: +91 9539193005

linkdln arif-kk-0b3456214

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- BOOTSTRAP
- JAVASCRIPT
- NODE IS
- REACT
- MONGO DB
- GIT

ARIF. K

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PROFILE

An ambitious and self-motivated web developer with a considerable technical skill who possesses self- discipline and ability to work with minimum of supervision. Able to play a key role in website development to ensure maximum accessibility, user experience and usability. A quick learner who can absorb new ideas and can communicate clearly and effectively.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMMERCE IN COMPUTER (BCOM-CA)

IN COMPUTER APPLICATION

YEAR OF PASSING - 2021

(2017-2021)

AT MADIN ARTS AND SCIENCE

COLLEGE, MALAPPURAM

KERALA

CGPA-5.0

12TH STANDARD (2015-2017)

At GHSS

OTHUKKUNGAL

MALAPPURAM(DIST), KERALA

PERCENTAGE - 82%

10TH STANDARD (2014-2015)

At PKMMHSS EDARIKKODE,

MALAPPURAM, KERALA

PERCENTAGE - 87%

EXTRACURRICULAR

- An active member in National Service Scheme(NSS)
- Student Cordinator of Computer Society of India.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Intern at LUMINAR TECHNOLABS

OCTOBER 2021 - present MEARN STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

Hands on Training in Ethical Hacking at AVODHA

JULY 2021-SEPTEMBER 2021

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

SHOPPING CART USING NODE JS

- It was a Web Based Application There used Mongo DB, Express JS, Handlebars, for Complete this project.
- At user Side They Can Purchase The Products And the Admin Side they can Add the Products and Sell them.
- The User Can Login With OTP Verification Using Twilio Library .
- · The Payment Method Used in this Project is RazorPsy

CHAT APP USING NODE JS AND REACT

- It was a Web Application, The Client Side is Completed with React and the Server Side is Used Node Js
- They Used Socket io Library For Communication Between Web Client And Servers

OLX CLONE USING REACT JS

- This Web Application Works Like Same Olx Process.
- This Web Application can be Sell Their Properties or Products.
- The Database is Used Firebase for Store The User Details,

User Verification, Store The Details of Products